<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on XINYI YANG</title>
    <link>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on XINYI YANG</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:43:58 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.yeralex.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Feeling in Tashkent</title>
      <link>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/feeling-in-tashkent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:43:58 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/feeling-in-tashkent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Tashkent, the capital of Uzbekistan, on the evening of October 22nd, because we just came from Almaty, so it is inevitable for me to compare these two Central Asian cities, I found the infrastructure of Tashkent is obviously better than Almaty in the way from the airport to the hotel, and it is more likely to Chinese infrastructure image. The Cyrillic alphabet is much less on the street while almost only Cyrillic letters can be seen in Almaty. And maybe because it is closer to the Middle East, it is also obvious that the religious influence is greater in Tashkent. Not only do more women wear headscarves, but also the overall style of dress and ethnic complexity are not as open and diverse as in Almaty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/company-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 13:47:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/company-finance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In small and medium-sized enterprises, there is a common phenomenon, that is, managers do not have a precise understanding of their company&amp;rsquo;s financial situation, so their perceptions of the actual business situation as if it were like a layer of fog covered eyes, they do not know how much money they earned, do not know how much money they owed or how much money others owed themselves in exact numbers, only a roughly estimated amount. There is no doubt that this is a long-term development problem of the enterprise that must be resolved, however, small and medium-sized enterprises are faced with the pressure of survival and trivialities, to solve this problem is not all “willingness” problem, after all, quite a lot of cases is “can and can not” problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visit in Almaty</title>
      <link>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/visit-in-almaty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 13:28:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yeralex.com/posts/visit-in-almaty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I arrived in Almaty, Kazakhstan on the morning of October 19, 2024, where the temperature in October was already around 0 degrees Celsius, and it was like crossing from summer to winter in one day after traveling from Jiangsu, where it was nearly 30 degrees Celsius.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the way from the airport to the hotel, I kept my eyes on the vehicles on the road, trying to catch those familiar car figures, and with the County&amp;rsquo;s iconic taillights coming into view, our Central Asia and Middle East inspection program officially started to bear fruit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
